<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colbal on Colbal | Small Business Technology Consultant  </title>
    <link>https://colbal.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Colbal on Colbal | Small Business Technology Consultant  </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 15:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://colbal.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>High-value content versus low-value content in web design</title>
      <link>https://colbal.com/posts/high-value-content-versus-low-value-content-in-web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colbal.com/posts/high-value-content-versus-low-value-content-in-web-design/</guid>
      <description>In the world of web design, the importance of creating high value content cannot be overstated. High value content not only engages and captivates visitors, but also contributes to building credibility and trust with the audience. It focuses on providing informative, relevant, and valuable information that meets the needs and interests of the target demographic. On the other hand, low value content can be detrimental to a website&amp;rsquo;s reputation and visibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big tech in a small world</title>
      <link>https://colbal.com/posts/big-tech-in-a-small-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 11:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colbal.com/posts/big-tech-in-a-small-world/</guid>
      <description>Big tech products and services are often designed with enterprise-level clients in mind, making them too expensive and complex for small business owners. Many small businesses may or may not have the same needs as a large corporation and may find it difficult to justify the high costs associated with these technologies. Additionally, small business owners often lack the necessary technical expertise and resources to fully utilize these tools effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Launching Your Own Blog on a Budget: Github, Netlify and Hugo</title>
      <link>https://colbal.com/posts/discover-the-secret-to-launching-your-own-blog-on-a-budget-github-netlify-and-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 10:48:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colbal.com/posts/discover-the-secret-to-launching-your-own-blog-on-a-budget-github-netlify-and-hugo/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction
2. The Details
3. Implementing
4. Conclusion, TLDR
1. Introduction The tech, an explanation of Github, Hugo and Netlify Github, Hugo and Netlify are powerful platforms that work hand in hand to help developers easily create and deploy static websites. In a nutshell, Github is a code repository platform that developers use to collaborate, Hugo is a static site generator, and Netlify is a cloud-based hosting platform. With Netlify, developers can quickly and easily deploy their Hugo-generated sites to a global content delivery network with just a few clicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source vs Close Source</title>
      <link>https://colbal.com/posts/open-source-vs-close-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 15:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colbal.com/posts/open-source-vs-close-source/</guid>
      <description>My take on the situation.
First, to ensure we are all on the same foot, lets define Open Source and Close Source.
Open Source is some product, whether that is software or hardware, that is made available with the full possibility or intention for the user to make changes.
Close Source, also called proprietary, is some product, whether that is software or hardware, in which any modification or changes can been seen illegal and can be subject to legal action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
